SHIRLEY YUE

UI DESIGNER

INFO

ADDRESS

Rhodes, Sydney NSW

PHONE

(+61) 0410-918-668

EMAIL

shirleyyuedi@gmail.com

VISA

Permanent Resident

PORTFOLIO

https://shirleydy.github.io/

SKILLS

Stroyboarding

Wireframing

Prototyping

User Research

Illustration

Basic 3D Modelling

TOOLS

Sketch

• • • • •

Photoshop

• • • •

Illustrator

After Effects

. . .

Cinema 4D

• •

Axure RP

...

Keynote

• • • •

LANGUAGES

Mandarin

English

CAREER OBJECTIVE

A User Interface designer with three years of experience in design field is seeking an opportunity to make beneficial contribution to a company with enthusiasm and commitment. Knowledgeable in user interface, user experience, prototyping, wireframing, illustrating and user research. Equipped with a diverse and promising skill set. Proficient in an assortment of technologies, including Sketch, Photoshop, Illustrator, After Effects, Cinema 4D and Azure RP. Able to effectively self-manage during independent projects, as well as collaborate in a team setting.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

User Interface Designer

Jiezi Technology Co.Ltd | China

June 2018 - Oct 2020

- Took most responsibilities from strategy to the design of the 'Meet' mobile APP, an information social platform.
- Created original graphics (landing pages, illustrations, sketches etc) for most projects.
- Worked with product managers on evaluating user requirements and providing high-quality design proposal.
- Designed and validated workflows and interfaces through iterations.
- Participated in the establishment and maintenance of the platform specifications.
- Worked with the marketing team to design banners, posters, H5 pages and other promotional campaigns.

Digital Graphic Designer

PartyBestbuy Pty.Ltd | Sydney

Aug 2016 - Oct 2017

- Took responsibility for product picture library management and refinement.
- Designed templates for product listings and established design specifications.
- Made original designs for advertising, branding and related promotional materials.
- Assisted in managing the company's website and acquiring and maintaining new customers.

EDUCATION

Master of Information Technology

The University of Sydney | Sydney

Jul 2014 - Aug 2015

Achievement: Scored a Distinction in Software Development in Java

Bachelor of Information Technology

Deakin University | Melbourne

Apr 2013 - Jul 2014

 Achievement: Scored High Distinction in Web Programming, Project Management Scored Distinction in Interactive Media Systems, Project